8 Games. 8 Players. 1 Winner.
The OctoGames is a thriller, action, horror film directed by Aaron Mirtes.
Eight contestants compete in eight deadly, classic children's games.
They seek fame beyond their wildest dreams, competing for the chance to take over the YouTube
channel of the famous yet elusive masked content creator known only as "JaxPro".
Carrie, played by Lacy Hartselle.
Squish, played by Cale Adcock.
AJ, played by Luv Patel.
Walt, played by Henry Haggard.
Maxine, played by Allison Shrum.
Ruth, played by Alice Raver.
Google Play Games is an online video gaming service by Google for
Windows 10 and 11, Chromebooks, and Android devices.
Google Play Games on Android, launched in 2013, features "instant play" games, gamer
profiles, saved games and achievements which give XP to level up.
The maximum level you can go is currently 99.
Google Play Games for PC Beta launched in 2021 with a curated set of
Android games optimized for Windows and Chromebooks.
The user gamer profile syncs across Google Play Games on PCs and mobile devices.
A Google Account is required to use most of the features Google Play Games has.
The film explores themes of 遊戲, 挑戰極限, 組團打怪.
The tone is dark and intense.